Finding Aid for the Yale Reports Transcripts PASC.0231
UCLA Library Special Collections
Yale Reports transcripts
1958-1971
UCLA Library Special Collections
Yale University News Bureau
PASC.0231
5.75 Linear Feet (6 boxes)
Yale Reports was a weekly radio broadcast review from Yale University (ca. 1955-1974). Collection consists 400-plus issues of radio broadcast transcripts spanning 1958-1971.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift in 1993.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9946590223606533
Biography
Yale Reports was a weekly radio broadcast review from Yale University News Bureau. The radio program, broadcast from WTIC Hartford, featured interviews and commentary on a variety of contemporary issues from 1955 to 1976. WTIC inaugurated the series as a replacement for Yale Interprets the News. Transcripts of Yale Reports radio programs were supplied free of charge as a public service of Yale University.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of transcripts from Yale reports, a weekly radio broadcast review presented by Yale University and WTIC. Includes over 400 issues spanning 1958-1971. Not all years are complete.
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged alphabetically by title/topic.
Public service radio programs -- Connecticut -- Periodicals.; Yale Reports (Radio program).
- [Untitled], 1/24/1971 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  General note
  Number: 578
- [Untitled], 1/5/1969 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  Number: 497
- [Untitled], 1/10/1971 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  Number: 576
- [Untitled], 11/1/1970 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  Number: 566
- [Untitled], 11/15/1970 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  Number: 568
- [Untitled], 11/8/1970 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  Number: 567
- 100 Years of Italian Independence III: Socio-Political Problems A Report on Western Sicily, 4/16/1961 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  Number: 226
- 91st Congress and the Presidency (The), 1/26/1969 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  Number: 500
- Academic Advisers in Washington, 5/12/1963 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Number: 289
- AIESEC: A New Approach to Foreign Exchange, 11/7/1965 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  Number: 372
- ALCOHOL AND THE CITIZEN I: THE CENTER OF ALCOHOL STUDIES, 9/20/1959 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  Number: 158
- ALCOHOL AND THE CITIZEN II: ALCOHOL AND THE HUMAN BODY, 9/21/1959 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  Number: 159
- ALCOHOL AND THE CITIZEN III: ALCOHOLISM, 10/4/1959 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  Number: 160
- ALCOHOL AND THE CITIZEN IV: ALCOHOLISM THERAPY, 10/11/1959 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  Number: 161
- ALCOHOL AND THE CITIZEN V: ALCOHOL, THE CITIZEN AND RESEARCH, 10/18/1959 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  Number: 162
- All of Human Society Is the City, 12/14/1969 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  Number: 533
- America and Russia and Israel and Egypt, 3/1/1970 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Number: 544
- AMERICAN DILEMMA, 1958 (The), 11/16/1958 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Number: 128
- American Woman (The), 1/24/1965 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  Number: 347
- An Analyst Looks at Adolescents, 4/6/1969 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  Number: 510
- Analysis of Election returns, 11/13/1966 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  Number: 411
- ANGRY YOUNG MEN JUST A JOURNALISTIC LABEL, 11/30/1958 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Number: 130
- Are We Fighting In Vietnam For the Will of Heaven?, 11/26/1967 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  Number: 452
- Art of Latin America Since Independence (The), 1/16/1966 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Number: 382
- Art of Writing (The), 5/26/1963 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Number: 291
- ART REFLECTS CRISES OF AN AGE, 11/23/1958 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Number: 129
- Athlete In the University: Hero or Mortal? (The), 1/23/1966 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Number: 383
- Athlete In the University: Hero or Mortal? II (The), 1/30/1966 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Number: 384
- Attitudes of Combat Soldiers (The), 3/5/1967 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  Number: 427
- Austria: Problems of Neutrality, 10/31/1965 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  Number: 371
- Automobiles, Accidents and the Insurance System, 6/28/1970 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  Number: 561
- Ballads Brought to Life: Loving Well and Faithfully, 12/22/1968 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  Number: 495
- Barghorn Case (The), 11/24/1963 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Number: 301
- Baseball and Monopoly, 6/12/1966 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  Number: 403
- Being Tolstoy's Daughter, 6/15/1969 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  Number: 520
- Benjamin Franklin and the Ladies of Paris, 10/30/1966 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  Number: 409
- Between Generations, 6/14/1970 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  Number: 558
- Big Power and Mini-Nation, 6/4/1967 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  Number: 440
- BIOLOGICAL BASIS OF HUMAN EVOLUTION I: THE MEANING OF DARWIN'S THEORY OF NATURAL SELECTION, 12/28/1958 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Number: 134
- BIOLOGICAL BASIS OF HUMAN EVOLUTION II: THE THEORY OF NATURAL SELECTION AS APPLIED TO MAN, 1/4/1959 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Number: 135
- Birth Control and Population Stability I, 3/20/1966 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  Number: 391
- Birth Control and Population Stability II, 3/27/1966 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  Number: 392
- A British Labor M.P. Looks at His Party, 2/12/1961 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Number: 217
- BRITISH ELECTIONS 1959, 10/25/1959 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  Number: 163
- British Liberal Party (The), 2/24/1963 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  Number: 278
- Busing - One Year Later I, 4/10/1966 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  Number: 394
- Busing - One Year Later II, 4/17/1966 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  Number: 395
- A Cadence of Poets, 6/29/1969 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  Number: 522
- CAN AMATEURISM SURVIVE?, 4/19/1959 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  Number: 150
- Can Black Parents Save Their Children From the Schools?, 10/20/1968 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  Number: 486
- Can Parents Run the School?, 4/14/1968 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  Number: 472
- A CHALLENGE FOR THE YALE UNDERGRADUATES, 1/17/1960 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  Number: 175
- CHALLENGE*, 1/24/1960 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  Number: 176
- CHANGING ROLE OF DIPLOMACY (The), 4/26/1959 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  Number: 151
- Changing South (The), 2/19/1961 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  Number: 218
- Chemical War Against Plants and People (The), 2/4/1968 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  Number: 462
- Child of the 21st Century, 2/22/1970 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Number: 543
- Children Think Politics - When?, 11/3/1968 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  Number: 488
- Children: Minority Without Rights, 3/22/1970 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  Number: 547
- Christian and Politics (The), 3/13/1966 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  Number: 390
- Church Militancy: Pro or Con?, 12/26/1965 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  Number: 379
- A Civil Police In a Civil Society, 5/25/1969 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  Number: 517
- Computers in Architecture: Unsolicited Knowledge and Unsolicited Problems, 2/14/1971 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  Number: 581
- Conant Report - II: The Education of American Teachers (The), 2/2/1964 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  Number: 311
- Conant Report: The Education of American Teachers - I (The), 1/26/1964 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  Number: 310
- Confluence of Knowledge - I (The), 5/6/1962 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  Number: 253
- Confluence of Knowledge - II (The), 5/13/1962 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  Number: 254
- Congress and U.S. Foreign Policy, 2/23/1964 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  Number: 314
- A Conservative Speaks: Barry Goldwater, 4/22/1962 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  Number: 251
- A Conservative Speaks: Barry Goldwater, 4/29/1962 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  Number: 252
- Consequences of News From Vietnam, 11/24/1968 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  Number: 491
- Conservative Response: Part I (The), 5/3/1970 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  Number: 553
- Conservative Response: Part II (The), 5/10/1970 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  Number: 554
- Contemporary Films, 4/14/1963 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Number: 285
- CONTEMPORARY ITALIAN LITERATURE I, 4/24/1960 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  Number: 189
- CONTEMPORARY ITALIAN LITERATURE II, 5/1/1960 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  Number: 190
- Contemporary Music, 11/10/1963 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Number: 300
- A Conversation With Congressman John Lindsay, 1/7/1962 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  Number: 236
- Conversation C.P. Snow - I, 1/28/1962 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  Number: 239
- Conversation C.P. Snow - II, 2/4/1962 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  Number: 240
- CONVERSATION WITH IRIS MURDOCH, 11/1/1959 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  Number: 164
- Couch and the Capsule: Biochemical Research in Psychiatry (The), 3/29/1970 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  Number: 548
- Covering America: A Primer of Foreign Correspondence, 11/20/1966 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  Number: 412
- Creativity and the Use of Drugs, 6/2/1968 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  Number: 479
- Creativity I, 3/7/1965 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  Number: 353
- Creativity-II, 3/14/1965 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  Number: 354
- A Critic Looks At the Theater Today, 5/29/1966 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  Number: 401
- Critic and the Arts (The), 5/24/1964 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  Number: 327
- "Crossroads Africa", 12/25/1960 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Number: 210
- Culture/Counterculture, 11/22/1970 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  Number: 569
- David Riesman: Teaching the Lonely Crowd, 12/4/1966 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  Number: 414
- De Gaulle Defended, 4/7/1968 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  Number: 471
- Defense of the Unpopular Case, 1/5/1964 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  Number: 307
- Designer's Dilemma (The), 5/20/1962 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  Number: 255
- Dialogue on Democracy, 3/29/1964 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  Number: 319
- Digging For Everything: Ecological Archeology, 2/15/1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Number: 542
- Disarmament: Variations on a Theme, 3/22/1964 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  Number: 318
- Doctor and the Treatment of Narcotics Addiction - I (The), 2/6/1966 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Number: 385
- Doctor and the Treatment of Narcotics Addiction II (The), 2/13/1966 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Number: 386
- Does Compromise Define Politics?, 10/12/1969 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  Number: 524
- Ecological Bank Account, 4/12/1970 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  Number: 550
- Economic Credibility In Washington and In the Press, 2/28/1971 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  Number: 583
- Economic Survey I: Governmental Responsibility, 3/17/1968 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  Number: 468
- Economic Survey II: Social Responsibilities, 3/24/1968 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  Number: 469
- Economics and History, 2/16/1969 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  Number: 503
- Economics of the City, 2/9/1969 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  Number: 502
- EMERGENCE OF THE CARIBBEAN REGION I: HAITI (The), 12/6/1959 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  Number: 169
- EMERGENCE OF THE CARIBBEAN REGION II: THE CARIBBEAN AS A REGION (The), 12/13/1959 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  Number: 170
- EMERGENCE OF THE CARIBBEAN REGION III: HIGHER EDUCATION IN THE CARIBBEAN (The), 12/20/1959 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  Number: 171
- EMERGENCE OF THE CARIBBEAN REGION IV: CULTURAL LIFE IN THE CARIBBEAN (The), 12/27/1959 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  Number: 172
- Emotional Reactions to Contraception, 5/26/1968 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  Number: 478
- Encountering Marc Chagall, 6/11/1967 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  Number: 441
- Enforcing Law In Changing American Cities, 2/11/1968 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  Number: 463
- Ethics and Medicine: Confidentiality, 3/10/1968 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Number: 467
- Ethics and Medicine: Consent and Human Experimentation, 2/25/1968 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Number: 465
- Ethics and Medicine: Control of Human Experimentation, 3/3/1968 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Number: 466
- Ethics of Death (The), 1/17/1971 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  Number: 577
- Europe and the Common Market, 12/29/1963 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  Number: 306
- An Evening With Isaac Asimov, 11/6/1966 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  Number: 410
- Evolution and the Envelope of Life, 6/8/1969 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  Number: 519
- Existentialism and Psychotherapy - I, 12/8/1963 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Number: 303
- Existentialism and Psychotherapy - II, 12/15/1963 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Number: 304
- Fascism - Neo-Nazism, 11/17/1968 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  Number: 490
- Fertility, Contraception and the Pill, 4/16/1967 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  Number: 433
- Five Days in April, 5/17/1964 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  Number: 326
- For Jazz, Keyboard, and the Blues Part I, 12/28/1969 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Number: 535
- For Jazz, Keyboard, and the Blues Part II, 1/4/1970 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Number: 536
- FORESTRY- A STUDY AND A PROFESSION II: FOREST MANAGEMENT, 2/28/1960 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  Number: 181
- FORESTRY- A STUDY AND A PROFESSION III:WOOD TECHNOLOGY AND UTILIZATION, 3/6/1960 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  Number: 182
- FORESTRY- A STUDY AND A PROFESSION IV: THE ROLE OF RESEARCH IN FORESTRY, 3/13/1960 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  Number: 183
- FORESTRY- A STUDY AND A PROFESSION V: THE FUTURE POTENTIALS OF FORESTRY, 3/20/1960 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  Number: 184
- FORESTRY- A STUDY AND A PROFESSION: SILVICULTURE- THE SCIENCE OF TREE GROWTH, 2/21/1960 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  Number: 180
- Freedom vs. Authority in Russian Literature, 10/13/1963 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Number: 296
- From Gogol, With Love, 1/11/1970 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Number: 537
- From the Election to the Inauguration, 11/10/1968 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  Number: 489
- From the Other End of the Spectrum: Some Thoughts on the Architectural Condition, 1/19/1964 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  Number: 309
- From Time to Time, 12/6/1970 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  Number: 571
- Frontiers in Human Genetics, 11/22/1964 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  Number: 338
- Frontiers in Human Genetics II, 11/29/1964 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  Number: 339
- Frontiers of Medical Research: Developing New Drugs, 1/27/1963 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  Number: 274
- Frontiers of Medical Research: New Techniques in Surgery, 1/20/1963 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  Number: 273
- Frontiers of Medical Research: Progress Toward Better Hearing, 2/3/1963 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  Number: 275
- Future of Man and Medicine I: The Three Faces of Medicine (The), 6/11/1961 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  Number: 234
- Future of Man and Medicine II: Research and the Mirage of Health (The), 6/18/1961 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  Number: 235
- Gardens of Laundry: The Cityscapes of John Sloan, 5/24/1970 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  Number: 556
- Genetics and Heredity, 3/9/1969 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  Number: 506
- GHANA AND UGANDA, 6/12/1960 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  Number: 196
- God, Man and Technology I, 4/23/1967 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  Number: 434
- Government and Politics in the New African Nations, 1/3/1965 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  Number: 344
- Government and the Arts - I, 5/27/1962 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  Number: 256
- Happy Birthday, Machiavelli, 6/1/1969 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  Number: 518
- Health Services: Too Important to Leave to the Doctors, 2/1/1970 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Number: 540
- An Historical Approach to the Cold War - I, 10/20/1963 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Number: 297
- An Historical Approach to the Cold War - II, 10/27/1963 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Number: 298
- House Out of Order, 12/12/1965 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  Number: 377
- How Educational Is Educational Television?, 3/26/1967 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  Number: 430
- How Shall We Pay For Legal Assistance to the Poor?, 1/22/1967 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  Number: 421
- Human Evolution, 4/11/1965 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  Number: 358
- IMAGE OF MAN IN CONTEMPORARY AMERICAN DRAMA I (The), 5/22/1960 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  Number: 193
- IMAGE OF MAN IN CONTEMPORARY AMERICAN DRAMA III: CHANGES IN THE AMERICAN THEATRE (The), 6/5/1960 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  Number: 195
- IMAGE OF MAN IN CONTEMPORARY AMERICAN DRAMA, II: TRAGEDY IN AMERICAN DRAMA (The), 5/29/1960 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  Number: 194
- Image of Man in the Contemporary Novel I: Anglo-American Post War Fiction (The), 1/26/1961 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  Number: 219
- Image of Man in the Contemporary Novel II: The Image of Man In Our Fiction (The), 3/5/1961 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  Number: 220
- Image of Man in the Contemporary Novel III: The "Anti-Hero" In the American Novel (The), 3/12/1961 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Number: 221
- Image of Man in the Contemporary Novel IV: Man and Society In the European Novel (The), 3/19/1961 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Number: 222
- Image of Man in the Contemporary Novel V: The Image of the Hero In French Novel (The), 3/26/1961 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  Number: 223
- Image of Man in the Modern French Theatre (The), 4/30/1961 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  Number: 228
- Images of Man: The Buddhist Image, 10/21/1962 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  Number: 260
- Images of Man: The Hindu Image, 10/28/1962 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  Number: 261
- Images of Man: The Islamic Image, 11/4/1962 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  Number: 262
- Images of Man: The Marxist Image, 10/14/1962 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  Number: 259
- In Darkest Publishing; Hunting Writers and Readers, 5/11/1969 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  Number: 515
- In Defense of the Useless Subject, 2/9/1964 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  Number: 312
- Insanity Defense (The), 12/17/1967 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  Number: 455
- Intellectual Underground I: Spain (The), 4/28/1968 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  Number: 474
- Intellectual Underground II: Russia and China (The), 5/5/1968 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  Number: 475
- Intellectual Underground III: America (The), 5/5/1968 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  Number: 476
- An Interview With C. Douglas Dillon, 5/5/1963 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Number: 288
- Interview With Dr. Wilder Penfield, 3/10/1963 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  Number: 280
- INTERVIEW WITH KOICHIRO ASAKAI, JAPAN'S AMBASSADOR TO U.S., 5/8/1960 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  Number: 191
- INTERVIEW WITH SIR LESLIE MUNRO, 1/21/1960 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  Number: 177
- Is a New Theology Possible?, 10/24/1965 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  Number: 370
- Is TV Destroying American Culture, 6/21/1970 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  Number: 559
- Italian Politics Today, 2/18/1968 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Number: 464
- Japan as a Superpower, 3/8/1970 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Number: 545
- Jarrel - Remembered By His Friends, 6/25/1967 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  Number: 443
- Jazz, 12/1/1963 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Number: 302
- Jules Feiffer's Engine of Anger, 10/27/1968 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  Number: 487
- Kingpins of Southeast Asian Politics: United States, China, Indonesia, 11/19/1967 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  Number: 451
- Last 100 Years of Italian Art and Architecture I (The), 4/2/1961 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Number: 224
- Last 100 Years of Italian Art and Architecture II (The), 4/9/1961 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Number: 225
- Law and Civil Disobedience: Is Civil Disobedience Ever Justified?, 10/25/1964 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  Number: 334
- Law and Civil Disobedience: The Role of Law in American Society, 11/1/1964 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  Number: 335
- Law and Civil Rights (The), 1/21/1962 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  Number: 238
- Law and Medical Research: What are the Limits? (The), 1/31/1965 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  Number: 348
- Law and the Nature of Society, 10/25/1970 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  Number: 565
- Law and World Order I: The Function of International Law (The), 12/4/1960 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Number: 207
- Law and World Order III: The Law Outer Space (The), 12/18/1960 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Number: 209
- Law and World Order: The Law in the Soviet Union (The), 12/11/1960 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Number: 208
- Law, Society and Money, 10/18/1970 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  Number: 564
- Law, Society and the Nature of Man, 10/11/1970 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  Number: 563
- Learning to Think In Our Native Language, 4/27/1969 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  Number: 513
- Legal Aid to the Poor: What Is Justice?, 1/15/1967 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  Number: 420
- Leslie Fielder on Teaching, 5/17/1970 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  Number: 555
- LIFE BEHIND THE IRON CURTAIN II: THE DILEMMA OF SOVIET SCHOLARS, 11/2/1958 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Number: 126
- LIFE BEHIND THE IRON CURTAIN III: KNOWING MORE ABOUT THE RUSSIANS, 11/9/1958 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Number: 127
- Light and Leaden Verse, 12/31/1967 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  Number: 457
- Light and Leaden Verse II, 1/12/1969 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  Number: 498
- Looking For a Decent Future, 11/2/1969 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  Number: 527
- Looking For Soma, Profane Research on Sacred Mushrooms, 11/27/1966 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  Number: 413
- Making of Poetry (The), 6/18/1967 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  Number: 442
- Making Things Work In Inner Cities, 10/13/1968 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  Number: 485
- Malaysia and the Balance of Power In Southeast Asia, 4/3/1966 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  Number: 393
- Man and the Machine - II, 2/21/1965 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  Number: 351
- Man-Made America: Chaos or Control?, 4/5/1964 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  Number: 320
- Mass Media and Criminal Justice I, 5/16/1965 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  Number: 363
- Mass News Media and Criminal Justice -II, 5/23/1965 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  Number: 364
- Matter and Anti-Matter, 12/18/1966 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  Number: 416
- Mayor Wagner Discusses New York City, 4/24/1966 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  Number: 396
- Midwives, Witches and Modern Medicine, 2/5/1967 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  Number: 423
- MILITARY STRATEGY AND DISARMAMENT I: MILITARY STRATEGY AND COEXISTENCE, 2/7/1960 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  Number: 178
- MILITARY STRATEGY AND DISARMAMENT II: U.S. MILITARY STRATEGY AND THE MISSILE GAP, 2/14/1960 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  Number: 179
- Modern Music and the Debt to Ives. Part I, 12/27/1970 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  Number: 574
- Modern Music and the Debt to Ives. Part II, 1/3/1971 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  Number: 575
- Morality and International Affairs, 4/18/1965 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  Number: 359
- Music of the 20th Century - I, 10/10/1965 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  Number: 368
- Music of the 20th Century - II, 10/17/1965 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  Number: 369
- NATIONAL PURPOSE AND THE ARTS AND SCIENCES II, 11/20/1960 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  Number: 205
- NATIONAL PURPOSE AND THE ARTS AND SCIENCES III, 11/27/1960 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  Number: 206
- NATIONAL PURPOSE AND THE ARTS AND SCIENCES: THE PRESIDENT'S COMMISSION ON NATIONAL GOALS, 11/13/1960 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  Number: 204
- Nationalism Observed, 1/18/1970 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Number: 538
- Nature and Chemicals Against Viruses, 3/16/1969 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  Number: 507
- New Evidence on the Origin of Man, 5/10/1964 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  Number: 325
- A New Look at Soviet Policy I, 2/20/1966 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  Number: 387
- A New Look at Soviet Policy II, 2/27/1966 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  Number: 388
- New Medicine For New Environments, 4/2/1967 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  Number: 431
- New Perspectives In Nursing, 3/6/1966 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  Number: 389
- A New Russia?, 11/8/1964 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  Number: 336
- New Voices of the Far East, 6/10/1962 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  Number: 258
- NEW WAYS OF LANGUAGE TEACHING I: LANGUAGE IS SOMETHING YOU SAY BEFORE YOU WRITE IT (The), 9/25/1960 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  Number: 197
- NEW WAYS OF LANGUAGE TEACHING II: NEW TEACHING MATERIALS FOR TEACHERS AND STUDENTS, 10/2/1960 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  Number: 198
- NEW WAYS OF LANGUAGE TEACHING III: DO THEY REALLY LEARN?, 10/9/1960 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  Number: 199
- Next Forty Years of American Theater I (The), 11/28/1965 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Number: 375
- Next Forty Years of American Theater II (The), 12/5/1965 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Number: 376
- No War in Space; The Moon Treaty and After, 5/28/1967 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  Number: 439
- Nuclear Art and Architecture, 12/11/1966 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  Number: 415
- Obscenity and the First Amendment, 6/19/1966 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  Number: 404
- On Drugs, 10/19/1969 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  Number: 525
- On Modern Art, 3/15/1964 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  Number: 317
- On Poetry, 5/31/1964 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  Number: 328
- On Teaching: Secondary Schools and Student Values, 11/18/1962 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  Number: 264
- On Teaching: What Happens in a Classroom, 11/25/1962 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  Number: 265
- On Teaching: What Happens in a School, 12/2/1962 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  Number: 266
- On Writing, 5/2/1965 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  Number: 361
- Opinion Polls, Computers, and the National Election - I, 10/4/1964 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  Number: 331
- Opinion Polls, Computers, and the National Election II, 10/11/1964 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  Number: 332
- Opinion Polls, Computers, and the National Election III, 10/18/1964 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  Number: 333
- Our Children's Burden: School Desegregation, 1/7/1968 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Number: 458
- Paleface Power: The Problems of Reservation Indians, 3/30/1969 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  Number: 509
- Paris in the Twenties, 4/25/1965 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  Number: 360
- Paul Hindemith: Life and Music at Yale, 12/27/1964 (Box 3, Folder 49)